Michael Lewellen

(469) 951-8107

<u>michaelnlewellen@gmail.com</u> <u>www.michaellewellen.com</u> | <u>github.com/cylon56</u>

Summary

Been involved in the blockchain space as an investor and consultant since 2012. Adept at analyzing blockchain projects to determine viability. Specializes in blockchain development and whitepaper review. Experienced in explaining complex computer concepts to business professionals and finding use cases for blockchain technology in modern systems.

Skills

- Fluent in Java, Solidity, and JavaScript. Some familiarity with C, C++, R and Python
- Experienced with Github, Visual Studio, IntelliJ, Vim, NodeJS, and MS Office
- Development experience on Windows and UNIX/Linux
- Completed B9Lab Ethereum Developer course covering Solidity, Truffle, and Web3

Work Experience

Founder and Principal Consultant CryptoCurrency Consulting, LLC

(October 2014 – present) Dallas, TX

- Founded a consulting firm for crypto in 2014: www.cryptocurrencyconsulting.com/
- Provided consultations for mining, wallet security, and cryptocurrency trading
- Gave technical talks of how Bitcoin and blockchains work.
- Developed digital tokens and applications on Ethereum.
- Provided whitepaper reviews and deployment guidance for Initial Coin Offerings (ICO)
- Reviewed and revised smart contracts to deploy and offer Justmake Token (JM) on Ethereum. Officially listed as advisor on the project: www.justmake.org/team/

Blockchain Developer Olypsis Technologies

(February 2018 - present) Richardson, TX

- Developed, tested and deployed Ethereum smart contracts for ICO's including Rewards.com.
- Worked with Thomson-Reuters to develop tax solutions using blockchain.
- Provided project management and recruitment of additional developers.

Co-Founder and COO PixelHash

(October 2017 - February 2018) Richardson, TX

- Co-founded PixelHash, a digital asset creation and management platform for blockchain.
- Built a proof of concept that integrates digital assets with video games on Ethereum.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science University of Texas at Dallas May 2019 Richardson, TX

Leadership Experience

President, Blockchain Club, UTD (2017 – present)

Event Organizer, Dallas Bitcoin Meetup (2013 - present)

Event Organizer, North Texas Blockchain Alliance (2017 - present)

BSA Eagle Scout, Troop 380, Longhorn Council, (2008 - 2015)

Technology Director, Financial Leadership Association, UTD, (2015 –2016)